A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, general correspondence, RG 2, 1940-1946 FA758
Rockefeller Archive Center
- General Correspondence, 1940
  - Scotland, 1940; 1940/405
    Scotland
    - Scotland, 1940 (Box 200, Folder 1418)
    - Scotland - Social Sciences, 1940; 1940/405.E
      - Scotland, 1940 (Box 200, Folder 1418)
  - Australia, 1940; 1940/410
    Australia
    - Australia, 1940 (Box 200, Folder 1418)
    - Australia - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1940; 1940/410.E
      - Australia, 1940 (Box 200, Folder 1418)
  - New Zealand, 1940; 1940/418
    New Zealand
    - New Zealand, 1940 (Box 200, Folder 1419)
  - Fiji, 1940; 1940/419
    Fiji
    - Fiji, 1940 (Box 200, Folder 1419)
    - Fiji - Nursing, 1940; 1940/419.C
      - Fiji, 1940 (Box 200, Folder 1419)
    - Fiji - Public Health Demonstration, 1940; 1940/419.J
      Public health
      - Fiji, 1940 (Box 200, Folder 1419)
  - Caribbean Region, 1940; 1940/420
    Caribbean Area
    - Caribbean Region, 1940 (Box 200, Folder 1419)
  - Guyana, 1940; 1940/423
    Guyana
    - Guyana - Tuberculosis, 1940; 1940/423.T
      - British Guiana, 1940 (Box 201, Folder 1420)
  - Belize, 1940; 1940/425
    Belize
    - British Honduras, 1940 (Box 201, Folder 1420)
    - Belize - Malaria, 1940; 1940/425.I
      - British Honduras, 1940 (Box 201, Folder 1420)
  - Canada, 1940; 1940/427
    Canada
    - Canada - (A-R), 1940 (Box 201, Folder 1420)
    - Canada - (S-Z), 1940 (Box 201, Folder 1421)
    - Canada - Nursing, 1940; 1940/427.C
      - Canada, 1940 (Box 201, Folder 1421)
    - Canada - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1940; 1940/427.D
      - Canada, 1940 (Box 201, Folder 1421)
    - Canada - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1940; 1940/427.E
      - Canada, 1940 (Box 201, Folder 1421)
    - Canada - Humanities and Arts, 1940; 1940/427.R
      - Canada, 1940 (Box 201, Folder 1421)
    - Canada - Social Sciences, 1940; 1940/427.S
      - Canada, 1940 (Box 201, Folder 1421)
  - Bermuda, 1940; 1940/430
    Bermuda
    - Bermuda - Health Services, 1940; 1940/430.K
      Public health administration
      - FOX-1 Fox, Leon A. and Baker, Harry L. "Sanitary Survey of Bermuda", 1940 (Box 560, Folder 3810)
  - Jamaica, 1940; 1940/437
    Jamaica
    - Jamaica, 1940 (Box 201, Folder 1421)
    - Jamaica - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1940; 1940/437.E
      - Jamaica, 1940 (Box 201, Folder 1421)
  - Trinidad, 1940; 1940/451
    Trinidad and Tobago
    - Trinidad, 1940 (Box 201, Folder 1421)
  - Grenada, 1940; 1940/455
    Grenada
    - Grenada, 1940 (Box 201, Folder 1421)
  - India, 1940; 1940/464
    India
    - India, 1940 (Box 201, Folder 1422)
    - India, 1940 (Box 201, Folder 1423)
    - India - (A-Z), 1940 (Box 201, Folder 1424)
    - India - Nursing, 1940; 1940/464.C
      - India, 1940 (Box 201, Folder 1425)
      - Public Health Nursing in India, 1933-1940 (Box 560, Folder 3811)
    - India - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1940; 1940/464.E
      - India, 1940 (Box 201, Folder 1425)
    - India - Health Services, 1940; 1940/464.K
      - PUT-1 Putnam, Persis "A Statistical Analysis of Data on Pollution in Ground Water Flowing Through Alkaline Quicksand in an area of Punjab, India", 1940 (Box 560, Folder 3812)
    - India - Yellow Fever, 1940; 1940/464.O
      - India, 1940 (Box 201, Folder 1425)
    - India (Mysore), 1940; 1940/464.1
      - Mysore, 1940 (Box 201, Folder 1425)
  - Iraq, 1940; 1940/470
    Iraq
    - Iraq - Malaria, 1940; 1940/470.I
      - Iraq, 1940 (Box 202, Folder 1426)
  - Africa, 1940; 1940/475
    Africa
    - Africa, 1940 (Box 202, Folder 1427)
  - North Africa Region, 1940; 1940/485
    Africa, North
    - Egypt, 1940 (Box 202, Folder 1427)
  - South Africa, 1940; 1940/487
    Africa, Southern
    - South Africa, 1940 (Box 202, Folder 1427)
  - France, 1940; 1940/500
    France
    - France - (A-L), 1940 (Box 202, Folder 1428)
    - France - (M-Z), 1940 (Box 202, Folder 1429)
    - France - Nursing, 1940; 1940/500.C
      - France, 1940 (Box 202, Folder 1430)
    - France - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1940; 1940/500.E
      - France, 1940 (Box 202, Folder 1430)
    - France - Humanities and Arts, 1940; 1940/500.R
      - France, 1940 (Box 202, Folder 1430)
  - Algeria, 1940; 1940/501
    Algeria
    - Algeria - Social Sciences, 1940; 1940/501.S
      - Algeria, 1940 (Box 202, Folder 1430)
  - Vietnam, 1940; 1940/509
    Vietnam
    - Vietnam, 1940 (Box 202, Folder 1430)
  - Asia, 1940; 1940/600
    Asia
    - Asia, 1940 (Box 202, Folder 1430)
  - China, 1940; 1940/601
    China
    - China - Administration, 1940 (Box 202, Folder 1431)
    - China - (C-P), 1940 (Box 202, Folder 1432)
    - China - (S-Z), 1940 (Box 203, Folder 1433)
    - China - Medical Sciences, 1940; 1940/601.A
      - China, 1940 (Box 203, Folder 1433)
    - China - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1940; 1940/601.E
      - China, 1940 (Box 203, Folder 1433)
    - China - Humanities and Arts, 1940; 1940/601.R
      - China, 1940 (Box 203, Folder 1433)
  - Japan, 1940; 1940/609
    Japan
    - Japan, 1940 (Box 203, Folder 1434)
    - Japan - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1940; 1940/609.E
      - Japan, 1940 (Box 203, Folder 1434)
  - Thailand, 1940; 1940/617
    Thailand
    - Thailand, 1940 (Box 203, Folder 1434)
  - Holland (Netherlands), 1940; 1940/650
    Netherlands
    - Netherlands, 1940 (Box 203, Folder 1434)
    - Holland (Netherlands) - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1940; 1940/650.E
      - Netherlands, 1940 (Box 203, Folder 1434)
    - Holland (Netherlands) - Respiratory Diseases, 1940; 1940/650.M
      Respiratory organs -- Diseases
      - Netherlands, 1940 (Box 203, Folder 1434)
  - Europe, 1940; 1940/700
    Europe
    - Europe, 1940 (Box 203, Folder 1435)
  - Austria, 1940; 1940/705
    Austria
    - Austria, 1940 (Box 203, Folder 1436)
  - Belgium, 1940; 1940/707
    Belgium
    - Belgium, 1940 (Box 203, Folder 1436)
  - Belgian Congo, 1940; 1940/709
    Congo (Democratic Republic)
    - Belgian Congo, 1940 (Box 203, Folder 1436)
  - Yugoslavia, 1940; 1940/710
    Yugoslavia
    - Yugoslavia, 1940 (Box 204, Folder 1437)
    - Yugoslavia - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1940; 1940/710.E
      - Yugoslavia, 1940 (Box 204, Folder 1437)
  - Bulgaria, 1940; 1940/711
    Bulgaria
    - Bulgaria, 1940 (Box 204, Folder 1437)
  - Czechoslovakia, 1940; 1940/712
    Czech Republic; Slovakia
    - Czechoslovakia, 1940 (Box 204, Folder 1437)
  - Denmark, 1940; 1940/713
    Denmark
    - Denmark, 1940 (Box 204, Folder 1437)
    - Denmark, 1940 (Box 204, Folder 1438)
    - Denmark - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1940; 1940/713.E
      - Denmark, 1940 (Box 204, Folder 1438)
    - Denmark - Social Sciences, 1940; 1940/713.S
      - Denmark, 1940 (Box 204, Folder 1438)
  - Scandinavia, 1940; 1940/716
    Scandinavia
    - Scandinavia, 1940 (Box 204, Folder 1438)
    - Scandinavia - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1940; 1940/716.E
      - Scandinavia, 1940 (Box 204, Folder 1438)
  - Germany, 1940; 1940/717
    Germany
    - Germany - (A-G), 1940 (Box 204, Folder 1439)
    - Germany - (H-Z), 1940 (Box 204, Folder 1440)
  - Greenland, 1940; 1940/718
    Greenland
    - Greenland, 1940 (Box 204, Folder 1441)
  - Hungary, 1940; 1940/750
    Hungary
    - Hungary, 1940 (Box 204, Folder 1441)
  - Italy, 1940; 1940/751
    Italy
    - Italy, 1940 (Box 204, Folder 1441)
    - Italy - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1940; 1940/751.E
      - Italy, 1940 (Box 204, Folder 1441)
  - Norway, 1940; 1940/767
    Norway
    - Norway, 1940 (Box 204, Folder 1441)
    - Norway - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1940; 1940/767.E
      - Norway, 1940 (Box 204, Folder 1441)
    - Norway - Social Sciences, 1940; 1940/767.S
      - Norway, 1940 (Box 204, Folder 1441)
  - Romania, 1940; 1940/783
    ROmania
    - Romania, 1940 (Box 204, Folder 1442)
    - Romania - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1940; 1940/783.E
      - Romania, 1940 (Box 204, Folder 1442)
  - U.S.S.R., 1940; 1940/785
    Soviet Union
    - U.S.S.R., 1940 (Box 204, Folder 1442)
  - Finland, 1940; 1940/787
    Finland
    - Finland, 1940 (Box 204, Folder 1442)
    - Finland - Nursing, 1940; 1940/787.C
      - Finland, 1940 (Box 204, Folder 1442)
  - Lithuania, 1940; 1940/788
    Lithuania
    - Lithuania, 1940 (Box 204, Folder 1442)
  - Poland, 1940; 02.1940/789
    Poland
    - Poland - Polish Exiles, 1940 (Box 204, Folder 1443)
    - Poland, 1940 (Box 205, Folder 1444)
    - Poland - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1940; 1940/789.E
      - Poland, 1940 (Box 205, Folder 1444)
  - Sweden, 1940; 1940/800
    Sweden
    - Sweden, 1940 (Box 205, Folder 1444)
    - Sweden - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1940; 1940/800.E
      - Sweden, 1940 (Box 205, Folder 1444)
  - Switzerland, 1940; 1940/803
    Switzerland
    - Switzerland, 1940 (Box 205, Folder 1445)
    - Switzerland - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1940; 1940/803.E
      - Switzerland, 1940 (Box 205, Folder 1445)
    - Switzerland - Humanities and Arts, 1940; 1940/803.R
      - Switzerland, 1940 (Box 205, Folder 1445)
  - Turkey, 1940; 1940/805
    Turkey
    - Turkey, 1940 (Box 205, Folder 1445)
    - Turkey - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1940; 1940/805.E
      - Turkey, 1940 (Box 205, Folder 1445)
  - Cyprus, 1940; 1940/809
    Cyprus
    - Cyprus, 1940 (Box 205, Folder 1445)
    - Cyprus - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1940; 1940/809.E
      - Cyprus, 1940 (Box 205, Folder 1445)
  - Palestine, 1940; 1940/825
    Palestine
    - Palestine, 1940 (Box 205, Folder 1445)
- General Correspondence, 1941
  - International, 1941; 1941/100
    - B-C, 1941 (Box 205, Folder 1446)
    - D-F, 1941 (Box 205, Folder 1447)
    - Fosdick, Raymond B., 1941 (Box 205, Folder 1448)
    - Fosdick, Raymond B., 1941 (Box 205, Folder 1449)
    - Fosdick, Raymond B., 1941 (Box 205, Folder 1450)
    - F-I, 1941 (Box 206, Folder 1451)
    - J-L, 1941 (Box 206, Folder 1452)
    - M-N, 1941 (Box 206, Folder 1453)
    - Nutrition Studies, 1941 (Box 206, Folder 1454)
    - O'Brien, D. P., 1941 (Box 206, Folder 1455)
    - P-S, 1941 (Box 207, Folder 1456)
    - S-Wal, 1941 (Box 207, Folder 1457)
    - W-Z, 1941 (Box 207, Folder 1458)
    - International - Medical Sciences, 1941; 1941/100.A
      - Staff Communications and International Affairs, 1941 (Box 207, Folder 1459)
    - International - Yellow Fever, 1941; 1941/100.O
      - Staff Communications and International Affairs, 1941 (Box 207, Folder 1459)
    - International - Social Sciences, 1941; 1941/100.S
      - Staff Communications and International Affairs, 1941 (Box 207, Folder 1459)
    - International - Tuberculosis, 1941; 1941/100.T
      - Staff Communications and International Affairs, 1941 (Box 207, Folder 1459)
  - United States, 1941; 1941/200
    - United States - (A-Am), 1941 (Box 207, Folder 1460)
    - United States - (Amer), 1941 (Box 207, Folder 1461)
    - United States - (An-Az), 1941 (Box 208, Folder 1462)
    - United States - (B), 1941 (Box 208, Folder 1463)
    - United States - (C-Cl), 1941 (Box 208, Folder 1464)
    - United States - (Co), 1941 (Box 208, Folder 1465)
    - United States - (Co-D), 1941 (Box 208, Folder 1466)
    - United States - (E-Fa), 1941 (Box 209, Folder 1467)
    - United States - (Fa-Fo), 1941 (Box 209, Folder 1468)
    - United States - (Fo-Ge), 1941 (Box 209, Folder 1469)
    - United States - (Gl-Gz), 1941 (Box 209, Folder 1470)
    - United States - (H-Ha), 1941 (Box 209, Folder 1471)
    - United States - Harvard, 1941 (Box 210, Folder 1472)
    - United States - (Ha-Hz), 1941 (Box 210, Folder 1473)
    - United States - (I), 1941 (Box 210, Folder 1474)
    - United States - (J-La), 1941 (Box 210, Folder 1475)
    - United States - (Le-Lz), 1941 (Box 210, Folder 1476)
    - United States - (M-Me), 1941 (Box 211, Folder 1477)
    - United States - (Mi-Mz), 1941 (Box 211, Folder 1478)
    - United States - (N-Na), 1941 (Box 211, Folder 1479)
    - United States - (Na), 1941 (Box 211, Folder 1480)
    - United States - (O-Ph), 1941 (Box 211, Folder 1481)
    - United States - (Pi-Re), 1941 (Box 211, Folder 1482)
    - United States - Refugee Scholars - (A-Be), 1941 (Box 212, Folder 1483)
    - United States - Refugee Scholars - (Bi-D), 1941 (Box 212, Folder 1484)
    - United States - Refugee Scholars - (E-Fr), 1941 (Box 212, Folder 1485)
    - United States - Refugee Scholars - (Fr-G), 1941 (Box 212, Folder 1486)
    - United States - Refugee Scholars - (H), 1941 (Box 212, Folder 1487)
    - United States - Refugee Scholars - (I-J), 1941 (Box 212, Folder 1488)
    - United States - Refugee Scholars - (K), 1941 (Box 213, Folder 1489)
    - United States - Refugee Scholars - (L-Ma), 1941 (Box 213, Folder 1490)
    - United States - Refugee Scholars - (Me-P), 1941 (Box 213, Folder 1491)
    - United States - Refugee Scholars - (R-Si), 1941 (Box 213, Folder 1492)
    - United States - Refugee Scholars - (So-Ve), 1941 (Box 213, Folder 1493)
    - United States - Refugee Scholars - (V-Wa), 1941 (Box 214, Folder 1494)
    - United States - Refugee Scholars - (Wa-Z), 1941 (Box 214, Folder 1495)
    - United States - Research Council on Problems of Alchohol, 1941 (Box 214, Folder 1496)
    - United States - (Re-Rz), 1941 (Box 214, Folder 1497)
    - United States - (S-So), 1941 (Box 214, Folder 1498)
    - United States - (Sp), 1941 (Box 214, Folder 1499)
    - United States - (T-Un), 1941 (Box 215, Folder 1500)
    - United States Government - (A-P), 1941 (Box 215, Folder 1501)
    - United States Government - (S-Z), 1941 (Box 215, Folder 1502)
    - United States - (Un-Z), 1941 (Box 215, Folder 1503)
    - United States - Medical Sciences, 1941; 1941/200.A
      - United States, 1941 (Box 215, Folder 1504)
    - United States - Nursing, 1941; 1941/200.C
      - United States, 1941 (Box 216, Folder 1505)
    - United States - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1941; 1941/200.D
      - United States, 1941 (Box 216, Folder 1505)
    - United States - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1941; 1941/200.E
      - United States, 1941 (Box 216, Folder 1505)
      - United States - (L-Z), 1941 (Box 216, Folder 1506)
    - United States - Public Health Education, 1941; 1941/200.L
      - United States, 1941 (Box 216, Folder 1507)
    - United States - Humanities and Arts, 1941; 1941/200.R
      - United States, 1941 (Box 216, Folder 1507)
    - United States - Social Sciences, 1941; 1941/200.S
      - United States, 1941 (Box 216, Folder 1508)
  - Alabama, 1941; 1941/201
    - Alabama, 1941 (Box 216, Folder 1509)
  - Alaska, 1941; 1941/202
    Alaska
    - Alaska, 1941 (Box 216, Folder 1509)
  - Arkansas, 1941; 1941/204
    - Arkansas, 1941 (Box 216, Folder 1509)
  - California, 1941; 1941/205
    - California, 1941 (Box 216, Folder 1509)
    - California - University of California, 1941 (Box 216, Folder 1510)
    - California - Medical Sciences, 1941; 1941/205.A
      - California, 1941 (Box 216, Folder 1510)
    - California - Humanities and Arts, 1941; 1941/205.R
      - California, 1941 (Box 216, Folder 1510)
    - California - Social Sciences, 1941; 1941/205.S
      - California, 1941 (Box 216, Folder 1510)
  - Canal Zone, 1941; 1941/206
    Canal Zone
    - Canal Zone, 1941 (Box 217, Folder 1511)
    - Canal Zone - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1941; 1941/206.D
      - Canal Zone, 1941 (Box 217, Folder 1511)
  - Colorado, 1941; 1941/207
    - Colorado - Social Sciences, 1941; 1941/207.S
      - Colorado, 1941 (Box 217, Folder 1511)
  - Connecticut, 1941; 1941/208
    - Connecticut, 1941 (Box 217, Folder 1511)
  - Florida, 1941; 1941/211
    - Florida, 1941 (Box 217, Folder 1511)
  - Georgia, 1941; 1941/212
    - Georgia, 1941 (Box 217, Folder 1511)
  - Illinois, 1941; 1941/216
    - Illinois, 1941 (Box 217, Folder 1511)
  - Kansas, 1941; 1941/219
    - Kansas, 1941 (Box 217, Folder 1512)
  - Kentucky, 1941; 1941/220
    - Kentucky, 1941 (Box 217, Folder 1512)
  - Louisiana, 1941; 1941/221
    - Louisiana, 1941 (Box 217, Folder 1512)
  - Maryland, 1941; 1941/223
    - Maryland, 1941 (Box 217, Folder 1512)
  - Massachusetts, 1941; 1941/224
    - Massachusetts, 1941 (Box 217, Folder 1512)
    - Massachusetts - Medical Sciences, 1941; 1941/224.A
      - Massachusetts, 1941 (Box 217, Folder 1512)
  - Mississippi, 1941; 1941/227
    - Mississippi - State Board of Health, 1941 (Box 217, Folder 1513)
  - Nebraska, 1941; 1941/230
    Nebraska
    - Nebraska, 1941 (Box 217, Folder 1514)
  - New Hampshire, 1941; 1941/232
    New Hampshire
    - New Hampshire, 1941 (Box 217, Folder 1514)
  - New Mexico, 1941; 1941/234
    New Mexico
    - New Mexico, 1941 (Box 217, Folder 1514)
  - New York, 1941; 1941/235
    New York (State)
    - New York, 1941 (Box 217, Folder 1514)
  - North Carolina, 1941; 1941/236
    - North Carolina, 1941 (Box 217, Folder 1514)
  - Ohio, 1941; 1941/238
    - Ohio, 1941 (Box 217, Folder 1514)
    - Ohio - Humanities and Arts, 1941; 1941/238.R
      - Ohio, 1941 (Box 217, Folder 1514)
  - Pennsylvania, 1941; 1941/241
    - Pennsylvania, 1941 (Box 217, Folder 1515)
    - Pennsylvania - Humanities and Arts, 1941; 1941/241.R
      - Pennsylvania, 1941 (Box 217, Folder 1515)
  - Philippine Islands, 1941; 1941/242
    - Philippine Islands, 1941 (Box 217, Folder 1515)
    - Philippine Islands - Medical Sciences, 1941; 1941/242.A
      - Philippine Islands, 1941 (Box 217, Folder 1515)
  - Rhode Island, 1941; 1941/244
    - Rhode Island, 1941 (Box 217, Folder 1515)
  - South Carolina, 1941; 1941/246
    - South Carolina, 1941 (Box 217, Folder 1515)
    - South Carolina - Malaria, 1941; 1941/246.I
      - South Carolina, 1941 (Box 217, Folder 1515)
  - Tennessee, 1941; 1941/248
    - Tennessee - State Board of Health - TVA, 1941 (Box 217, Folder 1516)
    - Tennessee, 1941 (Box 218, Folder 1517)
    - Tennessee - Hookworm, 1941; 1941/248.H
      - Tennessee, 1941 (Box 218, Folder 1517)
  - Texas, 1941; 1941/249
    - Texas, 1941 (Box 218, Folder 1517)
  - Utah, 1941; 1941/250
    - Utah, 1941 (Box 218, Folder 1517)
  - Virginia, 1941; 1941/252
    - Virginia, 1941 (Box 218, Folder 1517)
    - Virginia - Humanities and Arts, 1941; 1941/252.R
      - Virginia, 1941 (Box 218, Folder 1517)
  - Washington, 1941; 1941/253
    - Washington, 1941 (Box 218, Folder 1517)
  - West Virginia, 1941; 1941/254
    - West Virginia, 1941 (Box 218, Folder 1517)
  - Wisconsin, 1941; 1941/255
    - Wisconsin, 1941 (Box 218, Folder 1517)
  - Virgin Islands, 1941; 1941/257
    - Virgin Islands, 1941 (Box 218, Folder 1517)
    - Virgin Islands - Tuberculosis, 1941; 1941/257.T
      - Virgin Islands, 1941 (Box 218, Folder 1517)
  - South America, 1941; 1941/300
    South America
    - South America - Administration, 1941 (Box 218, Folder 1518)
    - South America - General File, 1941 (Box 218, Folder 1519)
    - South America - (A-Z), 1941 (Box 218, Folder 1520)
    - South America - Medical Sciences, 1941; 1941/300.A
      - South America, 1941 (Box 218, Folder 1521)
    - South America - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1941; 1941/300.D
      Science; Agriculture
      - MIL-1 Miller, H. M. "Diary of Latin American Visit", 1941 (Box 561, Folder 3813)
    - South America - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1941; 1941/300.E
      - South America - Reports, 1941 (Box 218, Folder 1522)
    - South America - Humanities and Arts, 1941; 1941/300.R
      - South America, 1941 (Box 218, Folder 1523)
    - South America - Social Sciences, 1941; 1941/300.S
      - South America, 1941 (Box 218, Folder 1523)
  - Argentina, 1941; 1941/301
    - Argentina, 1941 (Box 219, Folder 1524)
    - Argentina - Medical Sciences, 1941; 1941/301.A
      - Argentina, 1941 (Box 219, Folder 1525)
    - Argentina - Nursing, 1941; 1941/301.C
      - Argentina, 1941 (Box 219, Folder 1525)
    - Argentina - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1941; 1941/301.D
      - Argentina, 1941 (Box 219, Folder 1525)
    - Argentina - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1941; 1941/301.E
      - Argentina, 1941 (Box 219, Folder 1525)
    - Argentina - Hookworm, 1941; 1941/301.H
      - Argentina, 1941 (Box 219, Folder 1525)
  - Bolivia, 1941; 1941/303
    - Bolivia, 1941 (Box 219, Folder 1525)
  - Brazil, 1941; 1941/305
    - Brazil, 1941 (Box 219, Folder 1526)
    - Brazil - Yellow Fever, 1941; 1941/305.O
      - Brazil, 1941 (Box 219, Folder 1526)
  - Chile, 1941; 1941/309
    - Chile, 1941 (Box 219, Folder 1526)
    - Chile - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1941; 1941/309.E
      - Chile, 1941 (Box 219, Folder 1526)
  - Colombia, 1941; 1941/311
    - Colombia, 1941 (Box 219, Folder 1527)
    - Colombia - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1941; 1941/311.E
      - Colombia, 1941 (Box 219, Folder 1527)
  - Costa Rica, 1941; 1941/313
    - Costa Rica, 1941 (Box 219, Folder 1527)
    - Costa Rica - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1941; 1941/313.E
      - Costa Rica, 1941 (Box 219, Folder 1527)
    - Costa Rica - Tuberculosis, 1941; 1941/313.T
      - Costa Rica, 1941 (Box 219, Folder 1527)
  - Cuba, 1941; 1941/315
    - Cuba, 1941 (Box 219, Folder 1527)
  - Ecuador, 1941; 1941/317
    - Ecuador, 1941 (Box 219, Folder 1528)
    - Ecuador - Malaria, 1941; 1941/317.I
      - Ecuador, 1941 (Box 219, Folder 1528)
  - Guatemala, 1941; 1941/319
    - Guatemala, 1941 (Box 219, Folder 1528)
  - Mexico, 1941; 1941/323
    - Mexico, 1941 (Box 219, Folder 1528)
    - Mexico, 1941 (Box 219, Folder 1529)
    - FER-3, Ferrell, John A., Memo to R. B. Fosdick, January 27, 1941, FER-5, Ferrell, John A., Report on Visit to Mexico, March 14-April 13, 1941 (Box 561, Folder 3814)
    - Mexico - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1941; 1941/323.E
      - Mexico, 1941 (Box 219, Folder 1529)
    - Mexico - Humanities and Arts, 1941; 1941/323.R
      - Mexico, 1941 (Box 219, Folder 1529)
    - Mexico - Social Sciences, 1941; 1941/323.S
      - Mexico, 1941 (Box 219, Folder 1529)
  - Nicaragua, 1941; 1941/325
    - Nicaragua, 1941 (Box 220, Folder 1530)
  - Panama, 1941; 1941/327
    - Panama, 1941 (Box 220, Folder 1530)
    - Panama - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1941; 1941/327.E
      - Panama, 1941 (Box 220, Folder 1530)
  - Paraguay, 1941; 1941/329
    Paraguay
    - Paraguay, 1941 (Box 220, Folder 1530)
    - Paraguay - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1941; 1941/329.E
      - Paraguay, 1941 (Box 220, Folder 1530)
  - Peru, 1941; 1941/331
    - Peru, 1941 (Box 220, Folder 1531)
    - Peru - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1941; 1941/331.D
      Science
      - Peru, 1941 (Box 220, Folder 1531)
    - Peru - Humanities and Arts, 1941; 1941/331.R
      - Peru, 1941 (Box 220, Folder 1531)
  - El Salvador, 1941; 1941/333
    - El Salvador - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1941; 1941/333.E
      - El Salvador, 1941 (Box 220, Folder 1531)
  - Dominican Republic, 1941; 1941/335
    - Dominican Republic, 1941 (Box 220, Folder 1531)
  - Uruguay, 1941; 1941/337
    - Uruguay, 1941 (Box 220, Folder 1531)
    - Uruguay - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1941; 1941/337.D
      - Uruguay, 1941 (Box 220, Folder 1531)
    - Uruguay - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1941; 1941/337.E
      - Uruguay, 1941 (Box 220, Folder 1531)
  - Venezuela, 1941; 1941/339
    - Venezuela - Health, 1941 (Box 220, Folder 1532)
    - Venezuela - Health (A-Z), 1941 (Box 220, Folder 1533)
    - Venezuela - (A-Z), 1941 (Box 220, Folder 1534)
    - Venezuela - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1941; 1941/339.E
      - Venezuela, 1941 (Box 220, Folder 1534)
  - Great Britain, 1941; 1941/400
    - Great Britain - (A-G), 1941 (Box 220, Folder 1535)
  - England, 1941; 1941/401
    - Britain - Health - Jameson, Sir Wilson, 1941 (Box 220, Folder 1536)